Mumu,
come out.
Look what I bought for you.
Mumu.
Annie found where you were hiding,
and took away Mumu.
Didn't you promise me
to hold Annie back
while I was in the country?
Annie didn't take Mumu back to the old house,
but hid her.
At least now, if you want to get Mumu back,
you have to rely on yourself.
After you get Mumu back,
I can arrange for you to go to Malaysia.
You said you would lead me to the right path,
but I have lived in the abyss since I was born.
I'm sorry.
In the end, you still have to see
I become the monster I hate.
Only in this way can I defeat Annie.
Excuse me, are you Miss Jiang Li?
Yes, I am.
Oh.
Jiang Li.
You are more beautiful than the photos Jingmo stole.
Like a sharp dagger from the Warring States period.
No wonder
Jingmo is so persistent about you.
Grandfather Shen, you are in such a good mood.
Your grandson is in a coma in the hospital,
yet you're here fishing koi fish with ease.
Oh,
what a pity.
I thought I'd catch a big fish.
Oh,
no need.
Ah,
Shen Family men stick to their goals,
no matter how hard it is.
Among all the young men,
I like Jingmo the most.
Yeah.
Because he has that kind of spirit.
Hmph.
He's just like me back then.
I don't pity him.
Ah.
You don't have to feel guilty.
If you're not here to blame me,
what do you want from me?
I'll buy all the properties of the Lu Family
and give them to you
as a dowry.
When Jingmo wakes up,
you two get married
and live a happy life.
It's not good for you and Jingmo
to keep
chasing the past.
I appreciate your kindness,
but this incident
made me realize something.
Between Shen Jingmo and me, there's the blood he didn't spill
and the revenge I haven't completed.
I accepted his love,
but made him pay a price he shouldn't have.
So I decided to let go of this love.
Because when I pull the demon into the abyss,
I can't take him with me.
Girl,
you are as crazy
as Jingmo's grandmother.
If I were 50 years younger,
maybe
I would be Jingmo's rival in love.
Ah,
Grandpa Shen is really
as humorous as Shen Jingmo said.
When his grandmother split open
the door of the boardroom with an axe,
her eyes were also ablaze with the same fiery light as yours.
If you have any difficulties, come to me anytime.
This is for you.
What is this?
This is Shen Jingmo's trump card for you.
How do you have this?
Because Shen Jingmo anticipated everything that might happen.
He said your path to revenge was too dark,
and you needed to leave a light.
Aren't you afraid that I might betray you and Jiang Li
for money?
You know,
money is just a number
to me.
But you need atonement,
for yourself
and for the child in your belly.
So what do you want me to do?
This is a copy of all the materials.
I don't believe Jenny, a coward,
would easily tell Jiang Li where the materials are.
You suspect
Jenny also told Annie
what you were doing?
Jenny is a selfish person.
Everything revolves around her own interests.
For her,
rather than getting involved in the vortex,
it's better to tell both sides.
No matter which side wins,
she can profit from it.
Now that you already know,
why do you want me to keep this copy?
[Jiang Li's path to revenge is too dark,]
[I have to leave her a light.]
[And the file in your hand is the last trump card.]
[And you will do anything]
[to cover up the truth.]
[If I don't come back,]
[just give this to Jiang Li.]
You really don't plan to tell Jiang Li
why you help her at all costs?
If something really happens to you one day,
she will live a life of regret.
My notebook is in this file.
I was bullied because I was fat again.
Grandpa, the big bad guy, doesn't help me.
I'm so angry.
I'll beat you.
You are disobedient.
Stop.
The wild girl is coming. Run.
Run.
But today is different.
She said her name is Su Muli.
She not only helped me,
but also wanted to be my friend.
Alright.
A man should learn to protect himself.
You are so fat.
If you have the same courage as me,
you can be the leader of the children.
Alright.
You must be bullied because you cry too much.
You are a boy.
You should protect girls
when you grow up.
If you keep crying,
no girl will like you
when you grow up.
How did you get the scar on your hand?
I scratched it when I climbed out of a deep hole.
It doesn't matter.
My name is Su Muli.
What's your name?
My name is Shen...
Come on, you're so slow.
I'll call you Shen Xiaopang.
From now on,
I'll protect you.
If anyone bullies you,
come to the orphanage and find me.
Okay.
Su Mulili is my first friend,
and the only friend I have.
That summer,
She was a butterfly in my black-and-white world.
With the scar and the sunflower band-aid,
She was my childhood's only reason to laugh.
And she was the one I swore to protect
when I grew up.
But she was like a meteor in a summer night.
She disappeared before I had a chance to make a wish.
It's as if she had never appeared in my world.
She was as beautiful as a dream.
The past always has to be put down.
The journey of life is like a speeding car,
which needs to continue along the road called time.
But fate
becomes a speed bump on this journey.
The freshman ball is a hunting ground.
With your face and the background of Shen Family,
the Parisian socialites will fight for you.
I'm really not interested in these.
Who is she?
Su Muli,
A genius in the Department of Costume Design.
Charles's closed disciple.
I advise you not to have any thoughts.
An oil prince covered her dorm steps with a diamond necklace.
She directly reported him for sexual harassment.
Fate is like the interlaced lines on her drawing board.
After many years,
I finally found the sunflower girl I lost.
It's like a kite that has gone away after breaking the line.
Suddenly appears on the old tree at the doorstep.
Full of surprise and joy.
But because the old tree is too tall,
I just look daily for wind.
which can make it fall down
and come back to me.
Hey, beauty.
What's up, beauty?
Do you want to play with us?
What are you doing?
Come on, let's go.
Do you dare to play with us?
Let's go.
Hi.
Su Muli
Why do you smell so much of alcohol?
Wake up.
You are drunk. I'll take you back to the dormitory.
You men
all say sweet words with the mask of the devil.
Zhou Jian
I'll ruin you and the Lu family.
But I don't have the courage.
because I'm afraid of being rejected,
I never dare to get close to her.
I only dare to stand in the corner and watch her.
I guard her
and fulfill the oath I made alone in childhood.
I'm sorry.
You are
the junior who always peeps at me in the library.
Tell me,
who bullied you?
I'll crush them for you.
Maybe it was just her impulse after drinking.
Maybe she didn't remember anything
after she sobered up the next day.
But for me,
giving my first kiss to the girl I love
is a happy thing.
From then on,
I decided to face my heart with courage.
I walked to the riverbank with the flowers in my arms,
just like holding the hairpin I didn't dare to give her.
This time, I'm going to tell her
Shen Xiaopang has grown up to be someone who can protect her.
Hi.
Where's Su Muli? She didn't come to sketch today.
She dropped out of school.
Fate cut the thread again before I could speak.
We are like two ships that will never meet.
Even the lighthouse is stingy to give us intersecting light.
Fate is like a despicable magician.
who took my sunflower girl away a few years ago,
now puts Lu Xu's engagement ring on her,
and pushes her back into my world.
But this time, no matter what,
I want to try.
Because the crybaby in my heart twenty years ago
tells me in the depths of my soul
that this is the last chance God gives you.
I know what you are doing.
Jiang Li.
Su Mulie.
I don't expect to be the protagonist of your life,
but can you add a supporting role called Shen Jingmo
in your revenge script?